◇原字幕
制作人：EVA-FANS & 白月字幕组
校订人：@秋本凉
发布时间：2017-12-21 20:02
https://www.zimuku.cn/detail/98520.html
◇时间索引
00:11 视频出处
00:51 正片
原视频名：Komm, süßer Trump
原作者名：Venom Tube
视频来源：youtu.be/AQmr-EhBdfQ
原视频发布日期：20200307
字幕修改/压制：旋火
字体：思源宋体
无字幕版：b23.tv/av842798779
I know, I know I've let you down
我知道，我知道我令你失望了
I've been a fool to myself
我曾自欺欺人
I thought that I could live for no one else
以为自己一人也能活下去
But now through all the hurt & pain
但现在 历经所有的悲伤与苦痛
's time for me to respect
是时候尊重事实了
The ones you love mean more than anything
你所爱的人比一切都重要
So with sadness in my heart
所以持着内心的哀伤
(I) feel the best thing I could do
自己最该做的就是
is end it all and leave forever
结束这一切、永远离去
what's done is done it feels so bad
所做的都已无法挽回
what once was happy now is sad
往昔的快乐已化为悲伤
I'll never love again
我不会再爱了
my world is ending
我的世界已终结
I wish that I could turn back time
我希望自己能让时间倒转
cos now the guilt is all mine
因为现在一切都是我的错
can't live without the trust from those you love
离开你所爱之人的信任，我就根本无法生存
*你所爱之人=受新冠影响的老白男亲戚
I know we can't forget the past
我知道我们无法忘却过去
you can't forget love & pride
你也放不下你的爱与骄傲
because of that, it's killing me inside
正因如此，我才心如刀绞
It all returns to nothing
一切都化为乌有
it all comes tumbling down, tumbling down, tumbling down
一切都崩溃、崩溃、崩溃
It all returns to nothing
一切都化为乌有
I just keep letting me down, letting me down, letting me down
我只会一直让自己失望、失望、失望
In my heart of hearts
内心深处
I know that I could never love again
我知道自己不能再爱
I've lost everything
我已失去一切
everything
一切
everything that matters to me, matters in this world
与我和世界有关的一切
I wish that I could turn back time
我希望自己能让时间倒转
cos now the guilt is all mine
因为现在一切都是我的错
can't live without the trust from those you love
离开你所爱之人的信任，我就根本无法生存
I know we can't forget the past
我知道我们无法忘却过去
you can't forget love & pride
你也放不下你的爱与骄傲
because of that, it's killing me inside
正因如此，我才心如刀绞
It all returns to nothing
一切都化为乌有
it all comes tumbling down, tumbling down, tumbling down
就这样一切都崩溃、崩溃、崩溃
It all returns to nothing
一切都化为乌有
I just keep letting me down, letting me down, letting me down
我只会一直让自己失望、失望、失望
It all returns to nothing
一切都化为乌有
it all comes tumbling down, tumbling down, tumbling down
就这样一切都崩溃、崩溃、崩溃
It all returns to nothing
一切都化为乌有
I just keep letting me down, letting me down, letting me down
我只会一直让自己失望、失望、失望
tumbling down
崩溃
letting me down
让我失望
tumbling down
崩溃
letting me down
让我失望